<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.TDBEUROTV"
       name="TDB EURO TV"
       version="1.09"
       provider-name="TDB">
<requires>
<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
<provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>TDB EURO TV</summary>
<description>Multicultural TV</description>
<disclaimer>The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.TDBPORNO"
       name="TDB PORNO"
       version="1.15"
       provider-name="TDB">
<requires>
<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
<provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>TDB PORNO</summary>
<description>Must be 19+ and older!</description>
<disclaimer>The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.TDBRADIO"
       name="TDB RADIO"
       version="1.06"
       provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>TDB RADIO</summary>
    <description>Live streaming Music</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.TDBSIMPLE"
       name="TDB SIMPLE"
       version="1.01"
       provider-name="TDB">
<requires>
<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
<provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>TDB SIMPLE</summary>
<description>Live Streaming TV</description>
<disclaimer>The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.TDBTV"
       name="TDB TV"
       version="1.46"
       provider-name="TDB">
<requires>
<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
<provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>TDB TV</summary>
<description>Live Streaming TV</description>
<disclaimer>The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.TOMDABOMB"
       name="TOMDABOMB"
       version="1.03"
       provider-name="TOMDABOMB">
<requires>
<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
<provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>TOMDABOMB</summary>
<description>Live streaming Audio from www.tomdabomb.ca</description>
<platform>all</platform>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.tdbaddon" name="TDB REPO" version="1.01" provider-name="tdbaddon">
<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="TDB Addon Repository">
<info compressed="false">http://github.com/tdbaddon/tdbaddon/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
<checksum>http://github.com/tdbaddon/tdbaddon/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
<datadir zip="true">http://github.com/tdbaddon/tdbaddon/raw/master/zips</datadir>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
<summary>Wisely choose you Must!</summary>
<description>Download and Install Addons</description>
<platform>all</platform>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.xbmcbackup"
    name="TDB-Backup" version="10.02" provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
     <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="scheduler.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ar">إنسخ إحتياطياً قاعده بيانات إكس بى إم سى وملفات اﻹعدادات فى حاله وقوع إنهيار مع إمكانيه اﻹسترجاع</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Backup and restore your XBMC database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Добавката може да създава резервно копие на XBMC и възстановява (след това) Вашата база от данни и настройки, в случай на необходимост.</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Feu còpies de seguretat i restaureu la vostra base de dades de l'XBMC i dels fitxers de configuració en el cas de fallada o corrupció dels fitxers.</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Zálohování a obnovení XBMC databáze a konfiguračních souborů v případě chyby nebo poškození souborů.</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Sikkerhedskopiér og genskab din XBMC database og konfigurationsfiler i tilfælde af et nedbrud eller en ødelagt fil.</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Die XBMC Datenbank sichern und bei Dateiverlust oder Beschädigung wiederherstellen.</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Δημιουργήστε αντίγραφα ασφαλείας της βάσης δεδομένων και των ρυθμίσεων του XBMC για την πιθανότητα σφαλμάτων ή καταστροφής αρχείων.</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Backup and restore your Kodi database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Backup and restore your database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Backup and restore your database and configuration files in the event of a crash or file corruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Haz copia de seguridad de tu base de datos y configuración y recupera todo en caso de fallo.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Respalda y restaura tu base de datos y archivos de configuración de XBMC dado el evento de un cuelgue o corrupción de archivos. </summary>
    <summary lang="eu">XBMC datu-basea eta konfigurazio fitxategien babes-kopia egin kraskatze edo fitxategi hondamena saihesteko</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Sauvegarder et restaurer vos bases de données XBMC et vos fichiers de configuration en cas de crash ou de fichiers corrompus.</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Sauvegarder et restaurer votre base de données et vos fichiers de configuration XBMC dans le cas d'un plantage ou d'une corruption de fichier.</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Crear copia de seguranza e restaurar a base de datos e ficheiros de configuración de XBMC no caso dun fallo ou corrupción de ficheiros.</summary>
    <summary lang="he">גיבוי ושחזור מסד הנתונים וקבצי ההגדרות של XBMC במקרה של קריסה או קבצים פגומים.</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Sigurnosno kopirajte i obnovite vašu XBMC bazu podataka i datoteke podešavanja prilikom rušenja ili oštećenja datoteka.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Biztonsági mentés készítése az XBMC adatbázisról és a beállítófájlokról vagy állítsa helyre azokat egy rendszerösszeomlás vagy adatvesztés után.</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Cadangkan dan kembalikan basis data XBMC Anda beserta berkas konfigurasi apabila terjadi kerusakan atau korupsi berkas.</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Effettua il backup o ripristina il tuo database di XBMC e i file di configurazione qualora si verifichi una chiusura imprevista o un danneggiamento dei file.</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">システムのクラッシュやファイル破損に備えて、XBMC のデータベースや設定ファイルをバックアップ・リストアできます。</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">XBMC 데이터베이스와 설정 파일을 백업하고 복구합니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Atsarginė kopija katra atkuria jūsų XBMC duomenų bazę ir konfigūracijos failus avarijos ar failo sugadinimo metu.</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Back-up en herstel je XBMC database en configuratiebestanden in geval van een crash of bestandscorruptie.</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Sikkerhetskopier og gjenopprett dine XBMC-databaser og -konfigurasjonsfiler i tilfelle et krasj eller filkorrupsjon.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Stwórz kopię bezpieczeństwa oraz przywróć twoją bazę danych XBMC łącznie z plikami konfiguracyjnymi, w przypadku awarii lub uszkodzenia plików.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Crie cópias de segurança da base de dados do XBMC e dos ficheiros de configuração. Pode restaurar o conteúdo se ocorrer um crash ou corrupção de ficheiros.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Faça backup e restaure o banco de dados do XBMC e seus arquivos de configuração, no caso de falha ou corrupção de arquivo.</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Сохраняйте и восстанавливайте базу данных и конфигурационные файлы XBMC, чтоб не допустить потерю данных в случае аварии или повреждений файлов.</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Zálohovanie a obnova XBMC databázy a konfiguračných súborov pre prípad havárie alebo poškodenia súboru.</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Ta backupp av eller återställ din XBMC-databas och konfigurationsfiler i händelse av en krash eller filkorruption.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">备份和恢复 XBMC 数据库和配置文件，以防范系统崩溃或文件损坏问题。</summary>
    <description lang="ar">أسبق لك ان أضعت تخصيصاتك المفضله ورغبت لو كان بإمكانك نسخهم إحتياطياً ؟ اﻷن بات بإمكانك ذلك. يمكنك إستخراج قاعده بياناتك وقوائم التشغيل والملحقات وتخصيصاتك المفضله وغيره الى اى مصدر خارجى قابل للكتابه من قِبَل إكس بى إم سى او مباشرتاً الى نظام تخزين سحابى. يمكنك تفعيل النسخ اﻹحتياطى عند الحاجه او جدولته مُسبقاً</description>
    <description lang="be">Ever hosed your XBMC configuration and wished you'd had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by XBMC or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="bg">Някога да сте губили всички настройки, които сте правили по XBMC? А разполагахте ли с резервно копие? Е сега можете да създавате резервни копия само с едно кликване. Можете да изнасяте базата от данни, плейлистите, миниатюрите, добавките и други, на всяко място до което XBMC има права за писане или директно в Dropbox. Можете да настроите и автоматично създаване на копия през определен интервал от време.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Alguna vegada s'ha carregat la seva configuració de l'XBMC i ha desitjat tenir una còpia de seguretat? Ara pot fer-ho amb un simple clic. Pot exportar la seva base de dades, llista de reproducció, miniatures, complements i altres detalls de la configuració a qualsevol font que pugui ser escrita per l'XBMC o directament a l'emmagatzematge en el núvol Dropbox. Les còpies de seguretat es poden executar sota demanda o per mitjà d'un planificador.</description>
    <description lang="da">Har du prøvet at slette din XBMC opsætning, og ønsket at du havde haft sikkerhedskopi? Nu kan du få det med et enkelt klik. Du kan eksportere din database, afspilninglister, miniaturebilleder, addons og andre opsætningsdetaljer til enhver kilde, som er skrivbar for XBMC eller direkt til Dropbox cloud lager. Sikkerhedskopier kan køres manuelt eller via en tidsplan.</description>
    <description lang="de">Jemals deine XBMC Konfiguration zerschossen und dir dann gewünscht, dass ein Backup existiert? Jetzt kannst du eine Sicherung mit nur einem Klick erzeugen. Du kannst deine Datenbanen, Playlisten, Thumbnails, Addons und andere Details zu einem Ort deiner Wahl sichern.</description>
    <description lang="el">Σας έτυχε ποτέ να χάσετε τις ρυθμίσεις του XBMC και να εύχεστε να είχατε αντίγραφο ασφαλείας; Πλέον μπορείτε με ένα απλό κλικ. Μπορείτε να εξάγετε τη βάση δεδομένων, τις λίστες αναπαραγωγής, τις μικρογραφίες, τα πρόσθετα και άλλες λεπτομέρειες της εγκατάστασης σε οποιαδήποτε πηγή στην οποία μπορεί να γράψει το XBMC, ή απευθείας στο λογαριασμό σας στο Dropbox. Τα αντίγραφα μπορούν να γίνονται κατ' επιλογή ή μέσω προγραμματισμού.</description>
    <description lang="en">Ever hosed your Kodi configuration and wished you'd had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by XBMC or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Ever hosed your configuration and wished you'd had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by XBMC or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="en_US">Ever hosed your configuration and wished you'd had a backup? Now you can with one easy click. You can export your database, playlist, thumbnails, addons and other configuration details to any source writeable by Kodi or directly to Dropbox cloud storage. Backups can be run on demand or via a scheduler. </description>
    <description lang="es">¿Alguna vez te has cargado la configuración de XBMC y habrías deseado tener una copia de seguridad? Ahora puedes tenerla con un único click. Exporta tus base de datos, listas de reproducción, miniaturas, addons y resto de configuraciones a cualquier fuente accesible por XBMC o a tu almacenamiento en Dropbox. Las copias de seguridad pueden programarse o realizarse bajo demanda.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">¿Alguna vez haz echado a perder tu configuración de XBMC y haz deseado tener un respaldo? Ahora puedes tenerlo con un simple click. Puedes exportar tu base de datos, listas de reproducción, miniaturas, addons y otros detalles de configuración correspondientes a cualquier fuente que pueda escribir XBMC. Los respaldos pueden ser efectuados a pedido o mediante una programación temporal</description>
    <description lang="fr">Avez-vous déjà perdu votre configuration XBMC et espéré avoir fait une sauvegarde ? Maintenant, vous pouvez le faire en un simple click. Vous pouvez exporter vos bases de données, playlists, miniatures, addons et autres fichiers de configuration vers n'importe quel endroit accessible depuis XBMC.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Avez-vous déjà ruiné votre configuration XBMC et souhaité avoir une sauvegarde? Vous le pouvez maintenant en un seul clic. Vous pouvez exporter vos base de données, liste de lecture, imagettes, addiciels et autres détails de configurations vers n'importe quelle source inscriptible depuis XBMC ou directement vers le stockage en nuage Dropbox. Les sauvegardes peuvent être exécutées sur demande ou à l'aide d'un ordonnanceur.</description>
    <description lang="gl">De seguro que algunha vez eliminou a configuración do XBMC e desexou ter unha copia de seguranza?. Agora pode cun só clic. Pode exportar a súa base de datos, listaxes de reprodución, miniaturas, complementos e outros detalles da configuración a calquera medio escribíbel ou directamente ao Dropbox. As copias de seguranza pódense executar baixo demanda ou programadas.</description>
    <description lang="he">האם אי פעם נפגמו הגדרות XBMC וייחלת שהיה לך גיבוי ? כעת אתה יכול ליצור כזה בלחיצת כפתור קלילה. ניתן לייצא את בסיס הנתונים, רשימות ההשמעה, התמונות הממוזערות, הרחבות והגדרות נוספות לכל יעד שיש ל-XBMC הרשאת כתיבה לו או ישירות לשירות אחסון הענן דרופבוקס. ניתן לתזמן מראש גיבויים או להריצם ידנית.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Jeste li ikada oštetili vaša XBMC podešavanja i poželjeli ste ih obnoviti iz sigurnosne kopije? Sada to možete jednim klikom. Možete izvesti vašu bazu podataka, popis izvođenja, minijature, dodatke i ostale pojedinosti podešavanja na svaki izvor dostupan XBMC-u ili izravno na Dropbox oblak pohrane. Sigurnosno kopiranje se može pokrenuti na zahtjev ili u planiranom vremenu.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Sikerült már összekutyulni az XBMC beállításait és jó lett volna egy biztonsági mentés? Most megteheti egy kattintással. Exportálhatja az adatbázisait, lejátszáslistáit, könyvjelzőit, kiegészítőit és egyéb beállításokat bármely, az XBMC által írható tárhelyre vagy közvetlenül a Dropbox felhő tárolóba. A mentések kézzel vagy időzítetten indíthatóak.</description>
    <description lang="id">Pernah membuat berantakan konfigurasi XBMC Anda dan berharap Anda punya cadangannya? Sekarang Anda dapat melakukannya dengan klik mudah. Anda dapat mengekspor basis data, daftar putar, gambar kecil, addon dan rincian konfigurasi lainnya ke sumber mana saja yang dapat ditulis oleh XBMC atau langsung ke penyimpanan awan Dropbox. Pencadangan dapat dijalankan sesuai permintaan atau terjadwal.</description>
    <description lang="it">Hai mai distrutto la tua configurazione di XBMC ma non ne avevi una copia di backup? Ora puoi farlo con un semplice click. Puoi esportare il tuo database, le playlist, le anteprime, gli add-on ed altre configurazioni su ogni percorso accessibile da XBMC o direttamente su Dropbox. I backup si possono fare a richiesta o possono essere pianificati.</description>
    <description lang="ja">XBMCの設定が消えてしまい、バックアップをとっておけば... と思ったことはありますか？これからは1クリックで簡単にバックアップできます。データベース、プレイリスト、サムネール、アドオン、その他設定項目を、XBMC が書き込み可能なメディアに書き出せます。Dropbox クラウドストレージにも直接書き出せます。スケジューラによる自動バックアップと、オンデマンドでのバックアップの両方が使えます。</description>
    <description lang="ko">XBMC 설정 백업본이 있었으면 하고 원했던 적이 있습니까? 이제 한 번의 클릭으로 가능합니다. 데이터베이스, 재생목록, 썸네일, 애드온과 기타  세부 설정을 어디에나 내보내거나 직접 Dropbox 에  저장할 수 있습니다. 백업은 수동 또는 예약으로 실행할 수 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Kada naujinate ir konfiguruojate savo XBMC ar susimastėte, kad jums reikalinga atsarginė kopija? Dabar galite tai atlikti vienu spustelėjimu. Savo duomenų bazes, atkūrimą, miniatiūras, priedus ir kitas konfigūracijos failus galite eksportuoti iš bet kokio šaltinio. Atsarginė(-ės) kopija(-os) gali būti paleistos pareikalavus arba per tvarkaraštį.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Ooit je XBMC configuratie verknalt en gewenst dat je een backup had? Nu kan dat met een simpele klik. Je kunt je bibliotheek, afspeellijsten, miniaturen, addons en andere configuratie optes exporteren naar elke bron die door XBMC beschrijfbaar is of direct naar een Dropbox cloud opslag. Backups kunnen op verzoek of via een rooster gedraaid worden.</description>
    <description lang="no">Har du noen gang ødelagt XBMC-installasjonen din og ønsket at du hadde en sikkerhetskopi? Det kan du nå med et enkelt trykk. Du kan eksportere din database, spillelister, miniatyrer, utvidelser og andre konfigurasjonsdetaljer til enhver kilde som er tilgjengelig for XBMC eller til Dropbox. Du kan lage sikkerhetskopier ved behov eller med en timeplan.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Straciłeś kiedyś swoją konfigurację XBMC i marzyłeś o kopii zapasowej? Teraz już możesz i to w prosty sposób. Możesz eksportować swoją bazę, listy odtwarzania, miniatury, wtyczki oraz wiele więcej do dowolnego źródła bezpośrednio z XBMC. Kopia bezpieczeństwa może być uruchomiona na żądanie lub wg harmonogramu.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Já arruinou a sua configuração do XBMC e desejou ter feito uma cópia de segurança? Agora pode, com apenas um clique. Exporte a base de dados, listas de reprodução, miniaturas, add-ons e outras configurações para qualquer fonte acedível pelo XBMC. As cópias de segurança podem ser executadas manualmente ou por temporizador.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Sempre se preocupou com sua configuração do XBMC e desejou ter um backup? Agora você pode com um simples clique. Você pode exportar seu banco de dados, listas de reprodução, miniaturas, addons e outros detalhes de configuração para qualquer fonte gravável pelo XBMC ou diretamente ao armazenamento na nuvem Dropbox. Os backups podem ser executados sob demanda ou por agendamento.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Хотите получить резервную копию настроек XBMC? Теперь можете это сделать одним щелчком мыши. Вы можете выгрузить вашу базу данных, плейлисты, эскизы, дополнения и другую нужную Вам информацию и сохранить её с помощью XBMC или выгрузить в облачное хранилище Dropbox. Резервную копию можно сделать по требованию или запускать по расписанию.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Už ste niekedy poškodili konfiguráciu XBMC a priali si mať zálohu? Teraz môžete - na jeden klik. Môžete exportovať Vašu databázu, playlist, náhľady, doplnky a konfigurácie na ktorýkoľvek zdroj zapisovateľný XBMC. Zálohy môžu byť púšťané na požiadanie alebo plánovačom. </description>
    <description lang="sv">Har du någonsin tappat bort din XBMC konfiguration och önskat att du hade en backup? Nu kan du enkelt med ett klick. Du kan exportera din databas, spellista, minityrer, tillägg och andra konfigurationsdetaljer till valfri källa som är skrivbar för XBMC. Backupper kan köras på begäran eller via scheman.</description>
    <description lang="zh">你是否经常折腾你的 XBMC，因而希望能够有个备份？你可以把资料库、播放列表、缩略图、插件和其他配置细节导出到 XBMC 可以写入的任意位置。备份可以按需运行或通过计划任务执行。</description>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license></license>
    <forum></forum>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="skin.TDBFlow"
  version="1.01"
  name="TDB Flow"
  provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_VE">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fil">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fo">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="he">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="hy">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="km">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="rm">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="tg">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="th">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Basic Remote skin by TDB</summary>
    <description lang="af">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ar">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="be">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="bg">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="cy">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="da">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="de">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="el">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="en">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="es">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="es_VE">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="et">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="fil">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="fo">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="he">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="id">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="is">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="it">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ja">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="km">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Skin designed to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="lv">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="mk">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="no">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="sl">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="sq">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="tg">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="th">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="tr">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="uk">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="vi">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Skin designed  to be used on Android TV's with a basic remote.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="skin.TDBFlow-K"
  version="1.00"
  name="TDB FLow Kodi"
  provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">TDB Flow Kodi tema deur TDB(Kodi se standaard tema)</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">جلد "كونفليونس" من صنع TDB(الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى)</summary>
    <summary lang="be">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Облик от TDB(стандартния за Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Pell TDB Flow Kodi, per TDB(Pell per defecte del Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Vzhled TDB Flow Kodi od TDB(výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Croen TDB Flow Kodi gan TDB(Croen rhagosodedig Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="da">TDB Flow Kodi skin af TDB(Kodi's standardskin)</summary>
    <summary lang="de">TDB Flow Kodi Skin von TDB(Standard-Skin von Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το κέλυφος TDB Flow Kodi από τον TDB(προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi).</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="es">TDB Flow Kodi skin por TDB(skin por defecto)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">TDB Flow Kodi skin por TDB(skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Skin confluende por TDB(skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="et">TDB Flow Kodi rüü autorilt TDB(Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TDB Flow Kodi-ulkoasu TDB(Kodi:n oletus ulkoasu)</summary>
    <summary lang="fil">TDB Flow KodiTDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="fo">TDB Flow Kodi útsjónd av TDB(Kodi's vanliga útsjónd)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Thème TDB Flow KodiTDB Flow Kodi par TDB(thème par défaut)</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage TDB Flow Kodi par TDB(habillage par défaut de Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Pel TDB Flow Kodi por TDB(Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="he">המעטפת TDB Flow Kodi של TDB(ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">TDB Flow Kodi presvlaka autora TDB(uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TDB Flow Kodi felszín. Készítő: TDB(Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
    <summary lang="hy">''TDB Flow Kodi'' - տեսք՝ TDBկողմից (Kodi - հիմնական տեսք)</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Skin TDB Flow Kodi oleh TDB(Skin bawaan Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="is">TDB Flow Kodi eftir TDB(Sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Skin TDB Flow Kodi da TDB(Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">TDB Flow Kodi スキン by TDB(Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
    <summary lang="km">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">TDB Flow Kodi 스킨 TDB만듦 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">TDB Flow Kodi teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė TDB(Kodi numatytoji teminė išvaizda)</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">TDB Flow Kodi apvalks no TDB(Kodi noklusētais apvalks)</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">TDB Flow Kodi skin by TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Penyatuan, kulit daripada TDB(Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TDB Flow Kodi skin door TDB(Kodi's standaard skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="no">TDB Flow Kodi-skall av TDB(Kodis standardskall)</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">TDB Flow Kodi autorstwa TDB(domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema "TDB Flow Kodi" por TDB(Tema predefinido do Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Skin TDB Flow Kodi por TDB(Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="rm">TDB Flow Kodi skin da TDB(Kodi's default skin)</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Costum TDB Flow Kodi de TDB(costum implicit)</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обложка TDB Flow Kodi (стандартная обложка Kodi). Автор: TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">TDB Flow Kodi skin od TDB(predvolený skin Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Preobleka TDB Flow Kodi avtorja TDB(Privzeta preobleka za Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Maska TDB Flow Kodi nga TDB(maska kryesore së Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">TDB Flow Kodi, ett skal av TDB(Kodi:s standardskal)</summary>
    <summary lang="tg">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ аз ҷониби TDB(Пӯсти пешфарзи Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ชุดตกแต่ง TDB Flow Kodi โดย  TDB(สกินเริ่มต้นของ Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">TDB tarafından TDB Flow KodiTDB Flow Kodi dış görünümü. (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Обкладинка TDB Flow Kodi (стандартна обкладинка Kodi). Автор: TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Giao diện TDB Flow Kodi bởi TDB(Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TDB 开发的 TDB Flow Kodi 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">TDB 製作的佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
    <description lang="af">TDB Flow Kodi is die standaard tema vir Kodi 9.11 en op. Dit is 'n kombinasie van konsepte van 'n klomp gewilde temas, en 'n poging om hulle goeie idees te omvat en te integreer in 'n tema wat maklik behoort te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
    <description lang="ar">"كونفليونس" هو الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى اﻹصدار 9.11 وما فوق. هو خلط بين اشهر اﻷجلده الاخرى معاً ومحاوله لتبنى ودمج افكارهم للخروج بِنِتَاج يُفترض به ان يكون سهل اﻹستيعاب بمجرد النظر لمستخدمى إكس بى إم سى المبتدئين.</description>
    <description lang="be">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="bg">TDB Flow Kodi е стандартният облик на Kodi 9.11 и по-новите версии. Представлява смесица от концепциите на много от популярните облици. Целта е да се интегрират тези добри идеи в подходящ и удобен вид за хора, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="ca">TDB Flow Kodi és la pell per defecte del Kodi 14.0 i superiors. És una combinació de conceptes de moltes pells populars que intenta adoptar i integrar les seves bones idees en una aparença que sigui senzilla d'entendre i utilitzar per els nous usuaris de Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="cs">TDB Flow Kodi je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 9.11 a novější. Jedná se o kombinaci konceptů z mnoha jiných populárních vzhledů, která se pokouší uchopit a integrovat jejich dobré nápady do vzhledu, který by měl být pro nového uživatele Kodi jednoduchý na pochopení a používání.</description>
    <description lang="cy">TDB Flow Kodi yw croen rhagosodedig Kodi 9.11 ac uwch. Mae'n gyfuniad o gysyniadau o nifer o grwyn poblogaidd ac mae'n ymdrechu i gyfuno eu syniadau da hwy i groen ddylai fod yn hawdd i ddefnyddiwr cyntaf Kodi ei deall a'i ddefnyddio.</description>
    <description lang="da">TDB Flow Kodi er standardskin'et til Kodi 9.11 og senere versioner. Det er en kombination af koncepter fra mange populære skins, og det forsøger at omfavne og integrere de gode ideer i et skin, der er let for førstegangsbrugere af Kodi at forstå og bruge.</description>
    <description lang="de">TDB Flow Kodi ist der Standardskin ab Kodi 14.0. Er ist eine Kombination mehrerer unterschiedlicher Skin-Konzepte und versucht dabei die besten Ideen zu kombinieren, um einen einfachen Einstieg für neue Kodi-Nutzer zu ermöglichen.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το TDB Flow Kodi είναι το προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 9.11 και άνω. Είναι ένας συνδυασμός από πολλά δημοφιλή κελύφη, και επιχειρεί να συμπεριλάβει τις καλύτερες ιδέες τους σε ένα κέλυφος το οποίο είναι εύκολο σε αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi να κατανοήσουν και χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
    <description lang="en">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi 14.0 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="es">TDB Flow Kodi es la skin por defecto de Kodi 9.11 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchas skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellas en una skin que sea sencilla de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">TDB Flow Kodi es el skin por defecto de Kodi 9.11 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchos skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellos en un skin que sea sencillo de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">TDB Flow Kodi es el skin por defecto para Kodi 9.11 en adelante. Es una combinación de conceptos de varias skins populares, e intenta adoptar e integrar sus buenas ideas en un skin que debería ser fá de entender y usar para quienes usen Kodi por primera vez.</description>
    <description lang="et">TDB Flow Kodi on Kodi vaikerüü alates versioonist 9.11. TDB Flow Kodi on paljude populaarsete rüüde kombinatsioon, üritades omavahel siduda nende parimaid lahendusi, et saavutada esmakasutajale selget ja kergelt kasutatavat tulemust.</description>
    <description lang="fi">TDB Flow Kodi on oletusulkoasu Kodi:n versiosta 9.11 lähtien. Se on yhdistelmä useiden suosittujen ulkoasujen konsepteista, ja yritys omaksua ja integroida heidän hyvät ideat ulkoasuun, jonka pitäisi olla helppokäyttöinen ja -tajuinen kaikille Kodi:n käyttäjille.</description>
    <description lang="fil">Ang TDB Flow Kodi ay ang default skin ng Kodi 9.11 at pataas. Ito ay kombinasyon ng mga konsepto at pagsubok paghaluin ang mga mahusay na ideya mula sa maraming popular na skins para ito ay maging madali sa mga unang beses gumamit ng Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="fo">TDB Flow Kodi er vanliga útsjóndin, sum er brúkt í Kodi síðan útg. 9.11. Hetta er ein samansjóðan av fleiri hugtøkum. Ætlanin er at útsjóndin skal lætta um móttøku og nýtslu av Kodi fyri nýggjar brúkarar.</description>
    <description lang="fr">TDB Flow Kodi est le thème par défaut à partir de Kodi 14.0. Reprenant les concepts issus de plusieurs thèmes populaires, il est une tentative d'inclusion et d'intégration des meilleures idées afin d'en rendre la compréhension et l'utilisation faciles y compris par des débutants.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">TDB Flow Kodi est l'habillage par défaut pour Kodi 9.11 et ultérieur. C'est une combinaison des concepts issus de plusieurs habillages populaires et une tentative d'inclure et d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées en un habillage qui devrait être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="gl">TDB Flow Kodi é a pel predeterminada para Kodi 9.11 e posteriores. É unha combinación de conceptos de algunhas peles populares, e tenta abranguer e integrar  as súas mellores ideas nunha pel que sexa fácil de entender e utilizar para as usuarias que utilizan por primeira vez Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="he">המעטפת TDB Flow Kodi היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi. המעטפת הינה תוצר של אימוץ מאפיינים ממעטפות פופולריות רבות תוך רצון לשלב מאפיינים אלה למעטפת פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשי Kodi חדשים.</description>
    <description lang="hr">TDB Flow Kodi je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 14.0 naviše. To je mješavina koncepta iz mnogih drugih popularnih presvlaka, pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre osobine u presvlaku i da budu lagane za upotrebu i razumljive novim Kodi korisnicima.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A TDB Flow Kodi az alapértelmezett felszín a Kodihoz a 9.11-es verziótól kezdődően. Merít sok sok népszerű felszín elképzeléséből, megpróbálva vegyíteni a jó ötleteket úgy, hogy az könnyen kezelhető legyen a Kodival először találkozóknak is.</description>
    <description lang="id">TDB Flow Kodi merupakan skin bawaan untuk Kodi 9.11 dan selanjutnya. Merupakan kombinasi konsep dari beberapa skin populer, dan berusaha untuk merangkul dan menyatukan ide bagus mereka ke sebuah skin yang mudah dipakai dan dipahami oleh pengguna Kodi pertama kali.</description>
    <description lang="is">TDB Flow Kodi er sjálfgefið útlit Kodi 9.11 og nýrra. Það er samsetning hugmynda frá mörgum vinsælum útlitum og er tilraun til að fanga og innlima þær góðu hugmyndir í útlit þar sem hugmyndin er að skuli vera einfalt fyrir fyrir nýja Kodi notendur að skilja og nota</description>
    <description lang="it">TDB Flow Kodi è la skin predefinita di Kodi dalla versione 14.0 in poi. È una combinazione di elementi provenienti da altre skin popolari e cerca di integrare e coinvolgere tutte le loro grandi idee in una skin facile da usare e comprendere per l'utente inesperto di Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="ja">TDB Flow Kodi は Kodi 9.11 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。さまざまな人気のスキンのコンセプトを組み合わせ、ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際に便利に使えるようにしてあります。</description>
    <description lang="km">TDB Flow Kodi គឺ ជាស្គីនចំបងរបស់ Kodi 9.11 and about. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
    <description lang="ko">TDB Flow Kodi 는 Kodi 9.11 이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">TDB Flow Kodi yra numatytoji teminė išvaizda pradedant Kodi 9.11 versija. Tai daugelio populiarių teminų išvaizdų derinys. Bandymas priimti ir integruoti vartotojų idėjas į teminę išvaizdą katra turėtų būti lengvai suprantama  pirmą kartą naudojantiems Kodi</description>
    <description lang="lv">TDB Flow Kodi ir Kodi 9.11 un jaunāku versiju noklusētais apvalks. Tajā apvienota daudzu populāru apvalku koncepcija un centieni pieņemt un integrēt labākās idejas, lai jaunajiem Kodi ietotājiem to būtu viegli izprast un lietot.</description>
    <description lang="mk">TDB Flow Kodi е основниот изглед на Kodi 14.0 и нагоре. Тој е комбинација на концепти од повеќе популарни изгледи, и настојува да ги обедини и истакне нивните добри идеи во еден изглед разбирлив за почетници.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Penyatuan ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia merupakan gabungan konsep dari pelbagai kulit terkenal, dan berusaha untuk merangkumkan dan menyepadukan idea baik kulit-kulit tersebut menjadi satu kulit yang mudah difahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna baru Kodi .</description>
    <description lang="nl">TDB Flow Kodi is de standaard skin voor Kodi 15.0 en hoger. Het combineert de concepten van andere populaire skins, waarbij het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is.</description>
    <description lang="no">TDB Flow Kodi er standardskallet for Kodi 9.11 og oppover. Det er en kombinasjon av konseptene fra mange populære skall, og prøver å omfavne og integrere de gode idéene i et skall som bør være lett å forstå og benytte seg av for nye Kodi-brukere.</description>
    <description lang="pl">TDB Flow Kodi jest domyślną skóra dla Kodi w wersji 9.11 lub nowszych. Jest kombinacją pomysłów z wielu popularnych skór i próbą zawarcia tego, co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O tema "TDB Flow Kodi" é o tema predefinido do Kodi 9.11 e superior. É uma combinação de conceitos a partir de muitos temas populares e tenta integrar as boas ideias dos mesmos, num tema que deverá ser fácil de entender e utilizar para os novos utilizadores do Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">TDB Flow Kodi é a skin padrão do Kodi 9.11 e acima. É uma combinação de conceitos das mais populares skins, visando abraçar e integrar as boas ideias em uma skin  que seja fácil de entender e usar, destinada  aos usuários iniciantes do Kodi. </description>
    <description lang="ro">TDB Flow Kodi este costumul implicit pentru Kodi 9.11 și versiunile ulterioare. Este o combinație de concepte împrumutate de la mai multe costume populare, care încearcă să îmbrățișeze și să integreze ideile lor bune într-un costum care să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit de către utilizatorii Kodi începători.</description>
    <description lang="ru">TDB Flow Kodi — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 9.11. Она представляет собой сочетание концепций, взятых из многих популярных обложек, в попытке интегрировать их удачные идеи в обложке, которая была бы простой для использования и понимания новыми пользователями Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="sk">TDB Flow Kodi je predvolený pre Kodi 9.11 a vyššie. Je kombináciou konceptov z mnoho populárnych skinov a pokusom integrovať ich dobré nápady do skinu, ktorý by bol ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="sl">TDB Flow Kodi je privzeta preobleka za Kodi 9.11 in novejše. Je kombinacija konceptov mnogih priljubljenih preoblek in poskuša zaobjeti in integrirati njihove dobre ideje v preobleko, ki bi bila preprosta za uporabo in razumevanje tudi novim uporabnikom Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="sq">TDB Flow Kodi është maska kryesore për Kodi 9.11 dhe verzionet më të lartë. Është nje kombinim nga shumë maska e popullarizuar dhe përpjeket për të përqafuar dhe integruar idetë më të mira në një maskë që të jetë sa më lehtë në përdorim dhe kuptim për përdoruasit duke e përdorur Kodi për herë të parë.</description>
    <description lang="sv">TDB Flow Kodi är standardskal för Kodi 9.11 och senare. Det är en kombination av koncept från många populära skal i ett försök att använda och integrera flera goda idéer till ett skal som är enkelt för användare som precis har börjat använda Kodi att förstå och använda.</description>
    <description lang="tg">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ ҳамчун пӯсти пешфарз барои Kodi 9.11 ё версияи навтар истифода мешавад. Ин пӯст аз унсурҳои пӯстҳои машҳури дигар сохта шудааст ва ва ҳамаи фикрҳои беҳтарин дар як пӯст ҷамъ мекунад, то ки корбарони навомад тавонанд Kodi-ро ба осонӣ фаҳманд ва истифода баранд.</description>
    <description lang="th">TDB Flow Kodiเป็นสกินเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi 9.11 หรือสูงกว่า มันเป็นส่วนผสมของแนวคิดจากสกินที่ได้รับความนิยมและพยายามที่จะยอมรับและบูรณาการส่วนที่ดีของมันเข้าไปในสกิน ซึ่งน่าจะง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodiใหม่ ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งานได้ดี</description>
    <description lang="tr">TDB Flow Kodi Kodi 9.11 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. Birçok popüler dış görünümün kavramlarını bir araya getirip ilk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
    <description lang="uk">TDB Flow Kodi — це стандартна обкладинка Kodi, починаючи з версії 9.11. Концепції багатьох популярних обкладинок поєднано у спробі використати та інтегрувати їхні вдалі ідеї в обкладинці, що стала б зрозумілою та простою в застосуванні для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="vi">TDB Flow Kodi là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 9.11 and các phiên bản trở về trước. Đây là sự kết hợp các khái niệm đến từ các giao diện khác nhau nhằm hướng người dùng đến sự đơn giản và dễ sử dụng.</description>
    <description lang="zh">在 Kodi 9.11 之后的版本中 TDB Flow Kodi 是默认皮肤。它集合了许多流行皮肤的创意，力求把这些优点融合到一个皮肤中，使得首次使用 Kodi 的用户能更容易上手。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">TDB Flow Kodi 是從 Kodi 9.11 開始預設的佈景主題。它結合了許多受歡迎的佈景主題的概念，且試圖包含並整合它們的優點，使第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af">TDB Flow Kodi is die standaard tema vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar">"كونفليونس" هو الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى وإزالته قد تسبب مشاكل</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="be">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">TDB Flow Kodi е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">TDB Flow Kodi és la pell per defecte del Kodi, la seva eliminació pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">TDB Flow Kodi je výchozím vzhledem Kodi, jeho odstranění může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cy">TDB Flow Kodi yw croen rhagosodedig Kodi, gall ei dynnu achosi anhawsterau</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">TDB Flow Kodi er standardskin'et til Kodi. Fjernes det, kan der opstå problemer</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">TDB Flow Kodi ist der Standard-Skin für Kodi. Die Deinstallation kann zu unerwünschten Nebeneffekten führen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Το TDB Flow Kodi είναι το προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος για το Kodi, η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">TDB Flow Kodi is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">TDB Flow Kodi es la skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarla puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">TDB Flow Kodi es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">TDB Flow Kodi es el skin por defecto para Kodi, removerlo podría causar problemas</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="et">TDB Flow Kodi on Kodi vaikerüü. Selle eemaldamine võib põhjustada ootamatusi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fa_IR">TDB Flow Kodi پوسته پیش فرض برای نرم افزار kodi می باشد و حذف آن موجب مشکلاتی خواهد شد.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fi">TDB Flow Kodi on Kodi:n oletusulkoasu, sen poistaminen saattaa aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fil">Ang TDB Flow Kodi ay ang default skin ng Kodi. Ang pagtanggal nito ay maaring magdulot ng problema</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fo">TDB Flow Kodi er vanliga útsjónding brúkt av Kodi. Strikan kann viðføra brek.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">TDB Flow Kodi est le thème par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">TDB Flow Kodi est l'habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">TDB Flow Kodi é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causas problemas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">המעטפת TDB Flow Kodi היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr">TDB Flow Kodi je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">A TDB Flow Kodi az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="id">TDB Flow Kodi merupakan skin bawaan untuk Kodi, menghapusnya mungkin menyebabkan permasalahan</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="is">TDB Flow Kodi er sjálfgefið útlit Kodi, það getur orsakað vandamál að fjarlægja það.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">TDB Flow Kodi è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe comportare dei problemi</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ja">TDB Flow Kodi は Kodi のデフォルトスキンですので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">TDB Flow Kodi는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">TDB Flow Kodi yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lv">TDB Flow Kodi ir Kodi noklusētais apvalks, dzēšot to, var rasties problēmas</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">TDB Flow Kodi е основната маска, бришењето може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms">Penyatuan ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">TDB Flow Kodi is de standaard Kodi skin, het verwijderen van TDB Flow Kodi kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="no">TDB Flow Kodi er standardskallet for Kodi, å fjerne det kan skape problemer</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">TDB Flow Kodi jest domyślną skórą Kodi. Jej usunięcie może powodować problemy.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">O tema "TDB Flow Kodi" é o tema predefinido do Kodi, e removê-lo pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">TDB Flow Kodi é a skin padrão do Kodi, removê-la pode lhe causar problemas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ro">TDB Flow Kodi este costumul implicit pentru Kodi, dacă îl eliminați pot apărea probleme!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">TDB Flow Kodi — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">TDB Flow Kodi je predvolený skin pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">TDB Flow Kodi je privzeta preobleka za Kodi, njena odstranitev lahko povzroči težave</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sq">TDB Flow Kodi është maska kryesore së Kodi, fshirja e saj mund të shkaktoj çështje.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">TDB Flow Kodi är standardskal för Kodi. Att ta bort detta skal kan skapa problem.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tg">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ ҳамчун пӯсти пешфарз барои Kodi истифода шуда истодааст ва агар онро тоза кунед, мӯшкилӣ метавонад ба вуҷуд ояд</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="th">TDB Flow Kodi เป็นสกินเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tr">TDB Flow Kodi Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="uk">TDB Flow Kodi — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="vi">TDB Flow Kodi là giao diện mặc định của Kodi, loại bỏ giao diện này có thể gây ra lỗi cho chương trình</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">TDB Flow Kodi 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">TDB Flow Kodi 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="skin.TDBTouched"
  version="1.01"
  name="TDB Touched"
  provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false">
    <res width="1280" height="960" aspect="4:3" default="true" folder="4x3Hirez" />
    <res width="1706" height="960" aspect="16:9" folder="16x9" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Touched omslag deur TDB ontwerp om op raak skerm toestelle te gebruik</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">جلد ملموس من  TDB صمم ليستخدم على أجهزة شاشات اللمس</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Touched skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Облик от TDB за устройства със сензорен екран</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Touched es una pell dissenaya per TDB per ser utilitzada en dispositius tàctils</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Motiv Touched byl vytvořen TDB pro použití na zařízeních s dotykovou obrazovkou</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Touched-skin af TDB, designet til at blive brugt på touchscreen-enheder.</summary>
    <summary lang="de">"Touched"-Skin von TDB erstellt zur Nutzung auf Touch-Screen-Geräten</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το κέλυφος Touched από τον TDB, σχεδιασμένο για χρήση σε συσκευές με οθόνη αφής</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Touched skin by TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Touched es una skin diseñada por TDB para ser usada en dispositivos táctiles.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Touched es un skin diseñado por TDB para ser usado en dispositivos táctiles.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Skin Touched por TDB diseñado para uso en dispositivos con pantalla táctil</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Touched rüü autorilt TDB puutetundlikele seadetele</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Touched-ulkoasun tehnyt TDB, suunniteltu käytettäväksi kosketusnäytöllisissä laitteissa</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Thème Touched de TDB conçu pour être utilisé sur les périphériques à écran tactile</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Pel Touched por TDB deseñada para empregar en dispositivos táctiles</summary>
    <summary lang="he">סקין Touched עוצב ע"י TDB עבור מכשירי מסך מגע</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Touched presvlaka od TDB-a je dizajnirana za korištenje na uređajima sa zaslonima osjetljivim na dodir.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A Touched felszínt TDB tervezte, az érintőképernyős eszközökhöz.</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Skin Touched di TDB ideata per essere usata su periferiche touch screen</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Touched スキン by TDB（タッチスクリーン端末向け）</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">TDB가 만든 Touched 스킨은 터치 스크린 장치에서 사용하도록 디자인 되었습니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Lietimui jautri tema sukūrta  TDB skirta naudoti kompiuteriui, plančetei su sensoriniu ekranu</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Touched маска од  TDB дизајнирана за користење со екрани на допир</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Touched skin oleh TDB direka untuk digunakan pada peranti skrin sentuh</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Touched skin door TDB ontworpen voor aanraakscherm apparaten</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Touched skallet av TDB er designet for bruk på trykkfølsomme enheter</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Skórka wykonana przez TDB, przeznaczona dla urządzeń posiadających ekran dotykowy</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema Touched de TDB, preparada para o uso em dispositivos com ecrã táctil.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Touched por TDB concebida para ser usada em dispositivos com telas sensíveis ao toque</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Skinul Touched realizat de TDB pentru a fi folosit pe dispozitivele cu ecran de tip touch</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Сенсорная обложка  от TDB предназначена для использования на устройствах с сенсорным экраном</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Touched skin av TDB utformat för att användas på pekskärmsenheter</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Touched skin od TDB navrhnutý pre použitie na dotykových displejoch</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Preobleka Touched avtorja TDB je namenjena za uporabo na napravah z zaslonom na dotik</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Maska 'Touched' nga TDB, dizenjuar për tu përdorur me pajisjet me ekran me prekje</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Touched skal av TDB designat att användas på pekskärmsenheter</summary>
    <summary lang="th">หน้าตา Touched โดย TDB ได้ถูกออกแบบมาเพื่อใช้กับอุปกรณ์หน้าจอสัมผ้ส</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Touched skin; TDB tarafından dokunmatik ekranlarda kullanılmak üzere tasarlanmıştır</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Обкладинка Touched, створена TDB для пристроїв зі сенсорним екраном.</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Bộ skin Touched bởi TDB được thiết kế để sử dụng trên các thiết bị sử dụng màn hình cảm ứng</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện cảm ứng thiết kế bởi TDB được dùng trên các thiết bị cảm ứng</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">由TDB设计用于触屏设备的Touched皮肤</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Touched 是由 TDB 所設計用於觸控螢幕裝置的佈景主題</summary>
    <description lang="af">Omslag van die grond af op ontwerp om op raak skerm toestelle soos die iPad te gebruik</description>
    <description lang="ar">جلد صمم بالكامل ليستخدم على أجهزة شاشات اللمس مثل الـ iPad</description>
    <description lang="be">Skin designed from the ground up to be used on touch screen devices like the iPad</description>
    <description lang="bg">Обликът е разработен от нулата специално за употреба на устройства със сензорен екран</description>
    <description lang="ca">Pell dissenyada des de zero especialment per dispositius de pantalla tàctil, com l'iPad</description>
    <description lang="cs">Motiv vytvořený od základu pro použití na zařízeních s dotykovou obrazovkou jako iPad</description>
    <description lang="da">Skinnet er designet fra bunden til at blive brugt på touchscreen-enheder såsom iPad'en.</description>
    <description lang="de">Skin wurde von Grund auf neu erstellt zur Nutzung auf Touch-Screen-Geräten wie iPad</description>
    <description lang="el">Κέλυφος σχεδιασμένο εξ αρχής για χρήση σε συσκευές με οθόνη αφής όπως το iPad</description>
    <description lang="en">Skin designed from the ground up to be used on touch screen devices or Android TV's used with a Fly Mouse or Wireless Mouse.</description>
    <description lang="es">Skin creada desde cero especialmente para dispositivos táctiles, como el iPad.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Skin creado desde cero especialmente para dispositivos táctiles, como el iPad.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Skin diseñado para uso en dispositivos con pantalla táctil como el iPad</description>
    <description lang="et">Spetsiaalselt puutetundlikele seadetele nagu iPad kasutamiseks disainitud rüü</description>
    <description lang="fi">Ulkoasu on suunniteltu alustalkaen käytettäväksi kosketusnäytöllisissä laitteissa, kuten iPad</description>
    <description lang="fr">Thème conçu en essence pour les écrans tactiles tel que l'Ipad</description>
    <description lang="gl">Pel deseñada de cero para ser empregada en dispositivos táctiles</description>
    <description lang="he">הסקין עוצב עבור מכשירים עם מסכי מגע כמו האייפד</description>
    <description lang="hr">Presvlaka dizajnirana od temelja za korištenje na uređajima sa zaslonima osjetljivima na dodir kao što je iPad</description>
    <description lang="hu">A felszín elkészítésének célja az, hogy használható legyen az olyan érintőképernyős eszközökön is mint az iPad.</description>
    <description lang="it">Skin ideata per essere usata su periferiche touch screen come l'iPad</description>
    <description lang="ja">iPad などのタッチスクリーン端末専用に開発されたスキン</description>
    <description lang="ko">iPad 같은 터치 스크린 장치에서 사용하도록 완전히 새롭게 디자인한 스킨</description>
    <description lang="lt">Tema sukūrta naudojimui kompiuteriams, plančetėms su sensoriniu ekranu tokioms kaip iPad, Samsung, Asus ir t.t.</description>
    <description lang="mk">Маска наново дизајнирана за користење со екрани на допир како што е iPad</description>
    <description lang="ms">Kulit direka dari sifar untuk digunakan pada peranti skrin sentuh seperti iPad</description>
    <description lang="nl">Skin is geheel opnieuw ontworpen om gebruikt te kunnen worden op apparaten met een aanraakscherm zoals de iPad</description>
    <description lang="no">Dette skallet er designet fra bunn for bruk på trykkfølsomme enheter som iPad</description>
    <description lang="pl">Skórka została wykonana z przeznaczeniem na urządzenia dotykowe, takie jak iPad </description>
    <description lang="pt">Tema desenvolvido de raiz para ser usado em ecrãs tácteis de dispositivos como o iPad</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Skin concebida do zero para ser usado em dispositivos com telas sensíveis ao toque, como o iPad</description>
    <description lang="ro">Skin realizat cu scopul de a fi utilizat pe dispozitive cu ecran de tip touch precum iPad</description>
    <description lang="ru">Обложка разработана с нуля для использования на устройствах с сенсорным экраном, таких как iPad</description>
    <description lang="se">Skal utformat från grunden för att användas på pekskärmsenheter som till exempel iPad</description>
    <description lang="sk">Vzhľad navrhnutý od základu pre použitie na zariadeniach s dotykovým displejom, ako napríklad iPad</description>
    <description lang="sl">Preobleka je zasnovana popolnoma na novo za naprave z zaslonom na dotik, kot je iPad</description>
    <description lang="sq">Maskë dizenjuar posaçërisht për tu përdorur me pajisjet me ekran me prekje si iPad’i</description>
    <description lang="sv">Skal designat från grunden för att användas på pekskärmsenhter som t.ex. iPad</description>
    <description lang="th">หน้าตาได้ถูกออกแบบขึ้นมาใหม่หมด เพื่อนำไปใช้กับอุปกรณ์หน้าจอสัมผ้ส เหมือน iPad</description>
    <description lang="tr">iPad gibi dokunmatik ekranlı cihazlarda kullanılmak üzere sıfırdan tasarlanmış dış görünüm</description>
    <description lang="uk">Обкладинка розроблена з нуля і призначена для використання на пристроях із сенсорним екраном, наприклад iPad.</description>
    <description lang="vi">Bộ skin được thiết kế lại từ đầu để sử dụng trên các thiết bị cảm ứng như iPad, Surface</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Giao diện được thiết kế cho các thiết bị cảm ứng như iPad</description>
    <description lang="zh">完全为用于类似iPad的触屏设备而设计的皮肤</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">為了如 iPad 等擁有觸控螢幕的裝所重新設計的佈景主題</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af">Moenie hierdie omslag gebruik as daar nie 'n raak skerm of muis gekoppel is nie, of jy mag navigasie verloor</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar">لا تستخدم هذا الجلد إذا لم يكن لديك شاشة لمس أو الفأرة موصولة أو قد تفقد التوجيه</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="be">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">НЕ ползвайте облика ако устройството не е снабдено със сензорен екран или мишка, в противен случай ще загубите възможността за навигиране</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">No utilitzeu aquesta pell excepte si teniu una pantalla tàctil o un ratolí connectat, sinó podeu perdre la navegació</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Nepoužívejte tento vzhled pokud nemáte dotykovou obrazovku, nebo připojenou myš. Můžete ztratit kontrolu nad ovládáním aplikace</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Brug ikke dette skin medmindre du enten har en touchscreen eller mus forbundet, ellers kan du miste navigeringen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Verwenden Sie diese Skin nur wenn Sie einen Touch-Screen haben oder eine Maus angeschlossen ist, andernfalls kann die Steuerung ausfallen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Μην χρησιμοποιήσετε αυτό το κέλυφος αν δεν έχετε είτε μία οθόνη αφής ή ένα ποντίκι συνδεδεμένο διότι μπορεί να χάσετε τη δυνατότητα πλοήγησης</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">No uses esta skin a no ser que tengas un dispositivo táctil o un ratón conectado, puesto que puedes perder la posibilidad de moverte por las opciones.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">No uses este skin a no ser que tengas un dispositivo táctil o un mouse conectado, ya que puedes perder la posibilidad de moverte por las opciones.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">No uses éste skin a menos de que tengas una pantalla táctil o un mouse conectado o puedes perder la navegación</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="et">Ära kasuta seda rüüd, kui sul puudub kas puutetundlik ekraan või ühendatud hiir. Vastasel juhul võid kaotada navigeerimise võimaluse</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fi">Älä käytä tätä skiniä ellei sinulla ole kosketusnäyttöä tai hiirtä liitettynä, koska saatat</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">N'utiliser ce thème qu'avec écran tactile ou souris sous peine d'en perdre le contrôle</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">Non empregar esta pel a non ser que teña ben un dispositivo táctil ou un rato conectado. Pode perder a navegación.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">אל תשתמש בסקין זה אם אין ברשותך מסך מגע או עכבר מחובר או שתחווה בעיות ניווט</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr">Ne koristite ovu presvlaku ukoliko nemate zaslon osjetljiv na dodir ili spojeni miš, u suprotnom možete izgubiti upravljivost računalom</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Ha a felszínt érintőképnyő nélkül, vagy egérrel használod, nem fog működni a navigálás</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Non usare questa skin se non hai un touch screen o un mouse connesso, o potresi perdere la navigazione</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ja">タッチスクリーンやマウスが接続されていない端末でこのスキンを使うと、操作出来なくなる可能性があります。</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">터치 스크린이나 마우스가 없는 상황에서 이 스킨을 사용하지 마십시오. 탐색이 불가능할 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Šios temos vartoti negalima, nebent Jūs turite jutiklinį ekraną, arba prijungtą pelę kitaip Jūs galite prarasti naršymą/navigaciją</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">Не користи маска доколку немас екран на допир или маус, може да ја загубиш навигацијата</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms">Jangan guna kulit ini melainkan anda mempunyai skrin sentuh atau tetikus yang bersambung atau anda kehilangan navigasi</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Gebruik deze skin niet tenzij u gebruik maakt van een aanraakscherm of muis anders kan je de besturing verliezen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="no">Ikke bruk dette skallet med mindre du har en touch skjerm, eller en mus tilkoblet da du kan miste muligheten til å navigere i XBMC</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Nie używaj tej skórki jeśli nie masz ekranu dotykowego lub podłączonej myszki, w przecinym razie możesz stracić możliwość nawigacji</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Não utilize este tema se não tiver um ecrã táctil ou um rato, pois irá perder opções de navegação.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Não use essa skin a menos que você tenha uma tela sensível ao toque ou um mouse conectado, ou você pode perder a navegação</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ro">Nu folosiți acest skin dacă nu aveți un ecran de tip touch sau dacă nu aveți un mouse conectat sau veți pierde navigabilitatea</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Не включайте эту обложку, если вы не используете сенсорный экран или мышь, потому что может перестать работать навигация</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="se">Använd inte detta skal om du inte har endera en pekskärmsenhet eller om mus, annars kan navigeringen sluta fungera</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Nepoužívajte tento vzhľad, pokiaľ nemáte dotykovú obrazovku, alebo pripojenú myš, inak môžete stratiť kontrolu nad ovládaním aplikácie</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">Ne uporabljajte te preobleke, če nimate zaslona na dotik ali povezane miške, ker boste s tem izgubili možnost navigacije</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sq">Mos e përdorni këtë maskë nëse nuk keni, ose ekran me prekje, ose maus te lidhur, përndryshe mund të humbni aftësinë për të naviguar</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Använd inte detta skal om du inte har endera en pekskärmsenhet eller en mus ansluten, annars kan du tappa bort navigeringen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="th">อย่าได้ใช้หน้าตานี้ จนกว่าคุณจะมี หน้าจอสัมผัส หรือ เมาส์ อย่างใดอย่างหนึ่งเชื่อมต่ออยู่ ไม่เช่นนั้นคุณจะสูญเสียการควบคุม</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tr">Bir dokunmatik ekranınız ya da fareniz olmadan bu dış görünümü kullanmayın, kontrolü kaybedebilirsiniz.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="uk">Використовуйте цю обкладинку, лише якщо ваш пристрій обладнано сенсорним екраном або мишею. Інакше ви можете втратити можливість керування.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="vi">Không sử dụng skin này trừ khi là bạn đang sử dụng màn hình cảm ứng hoặc sử dụng chuột để tránh trường hợp mất điều khiển</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Không sử dụng giao diện này trừ khi bạn có màn hình cảm ứng hoặc chuột được kết nối hoặc bạn mất điều khiển định hướng</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">在非触屏且没有鼠标控制的情况下使用此皮肤会造成无法控制设备</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">除非你有觸控螢幕或滑鼠連接，否則請不要使用這個佈景主題，不然你會無法控制 XBMC。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="skin.TDBTouched-K"
  version="1.0.0"
  name="TDB Touched Kodi"
  provider-name="TDB">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false">
    <res width="1280" height="960" aspect="4:3" default="true" folder="4x3Hirez" />
    <res width="1706" height="960" aspect="16:9" folder="16x9" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Touched omslag deur TDB ontwerp om op raak skerm toestelle te gebruik</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">جلد ملموس من  TDB صمم ليستخدم على أجهزة شاشات اللمس</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Touched skin by TDB designed to be used on touch screen devices</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Облик от TDB за устройства със сензорен екран</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Touched es una pell dissenaya per TDB per ser utilitzada en dispositius tàctils</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Motiv Touched byl vytvořen TDB pro použití na zařízeních s dotykovou obrazovkou</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Touched skin gan TDB wedi ei gynllunio ar gyfer defnydd ar ddyfeisiau sgrin cyffwrdd</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Touched-skin af TDB, designet til at blive brugt på touchscreen-enheder.</summary>
    <summary lang="de">"Touched"-Skin von TDB erstellt zur Nutzung auf Touch-Screen-Geräten</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το κέλυφος Touched από τον TDB, σχεδιασμένο για χρήση σε συσκευές με οθόνη αφής</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Touched skin by TDB designed to be used on touch screen devices</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Touched skin by TDB designed to be used on touch screen devices</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Touched skin by TDB designed to be used on touch screen devices</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Touched es una skin diseñada por TDB para ser usada en dispositivos táctiles.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Touched es un skin diseñado por TDB para ser usado en dispositivos táctiles.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Skin Touched por TDB diseñado para uso en dispositivos con pantalla táctil</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Touched rüü autorilt TDB puutetundlikele seadetele</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Touched-ulkoasun tehnyt TDB, suunniteltu käytettäväksi kosketusnäytöllisissä laitteissa</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Thème Touched de TDB conçu pour être utilisé sur les périphériques à écran tactile</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">L'habillage Touched par TDB conçu pour être utilisé sur des appareils à écran tactile</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Pel Touched por TDB deseñada para empregar en dispositivos táctiles</summary>
    <summary lang="he">המעטפת Touched של TDB המיועדת למכשירים בעלי מסך מגע</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Touched presvlaka od TDB-a je dizajnirana za korištenje na uređajima sa zaslonima osjetljivim na dodir.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">A Touched felszínt TDB tervezte, az érintőképernyős eszközökhöz.</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Touched viðmót eftir TDB hannað til að verða notað af tækjum með snertiskjá</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Skin Touched di TDB ideata per essere usata su periferiche touch screen</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Touched スキン by TDB（タッチスクリーン端末向け）</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">TDB가 만든 Touched 스킨은 터치 스크린 장치에서 사용하도록 디자인 되었습니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Lietimui jautri tema sukūrta  TDB skirta naudoti kompiuteriui, plančetei su sensoriniu ekranu</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">Touched apvalks no TDB dizainēts izmantošanai skārienekrāna ierīcēs</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Touched маска од  TDB дизајнирана за користење со екрани на допир</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Touched skin oleh TDB direka untuk digunakan pada peranti skrin sentuh</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Touched skin door TDB ontworpen voor aanraakscherm apparaten</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Touched skallet av TDB er designet for bruk på trykkfølsomme enheter</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Skórka autorstwa TDB zaprojektowana dla urządzeń z ekranem dotykowym</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema Touched de TDB, preparada para o uso em dispositivos com ecrã táctil.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Touched por TDB concebida para ser usada em dispositivos com telas sensíveis ao toque</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Skinul Touched realizat de TDB pentru a fi folosit pe dispozitivele cu ecran de tip touch</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обложка Touched от TDB предназначена для использования на устройствах с сенсорным экраном.</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Touched skin av TDB utformat för att användas på pekskärmsenheter</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Touched skin od TDB navrhnutý pre použitie na dotykových displejoch</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Preobleka Touched avtorja TDB je namenjena za uporabo na napravah z zaslonom na dotik</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Maska 'Touched' nga TDB, dizenjuar për tu përdorur me pajisjet me ekran me prekje</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Touched skal av TDB designat att användas på pekskärmsenheter</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">தொடுதிரை சாதனத்திற்கான அலங்காரம் - தயாரிப்பு TDB</summary>
    <summary lang="th">หน้าตา Touched โดย TDB ได้ถูกออกแบบมาเพื่อใช้กับอุปกรณ์หน้าจอสัมผ้ส</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Touched skin; TDB tarafından dokunmatik ekranlarda kullanılmak üzere tasarlanmıştır</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Обкладинка Touched, створена TDB для пристроїв зі сенсорним екраном.</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Bộ skin Touched bởi TDB được thiết kế để sử dụng trên các thiết bị sử dụng màn hình cảm ứng</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">由TDB设计用于触屏设备的Touched皮肤</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Touched 是由 TDB 所設計用於觸控螢幕裝置的佈景主題</summary>
    <description lang="af">Omslag van die grond af op ontwerp om op raak skerm toestelle soos die iPad te gebruik</description>
    <description lang="ar">جلد صمم بالكامل ليستخدم على أجهزة شاشات اللمس مثل الـ iPad</description>
    <description lang="be">Skin designed from the ground up to be used on touch screen devices like the iPad</description>
    <description lang="bg">Обликът е разработен от нулата специално за употреба на устройства със сензорен екран</description>
    <description lang="ca">Pell dissenyada des de zero especialment per dispositius de pantalla tàctil, com l'iPad</description>
    <description lang="cs">Motiv vytvořený od základu pro použití na zařízeních s dotykovou obrazovkou jako iPad</description>
    <description lang="cy">Croen wedi ei gynllunio o'r cychwyn i'w ddefnyddio ar ddyfeisiau sgrin cyffwrdd fel yr iPad</description>
    <description lang="da">Skinnet er designet fra bunden til at blive brugt på touchscreen-enheder såsom iPad'en.</description>
    <description lang="de">Skin wurde von Grund auf neu erstellt zur Nutzung auf Touch-Screen-Geräten wie iPad</description>
    <description lang="el">Κέλυφος σχεδιασμένο εξ αρχής για χρήση σε συσκευές με οθόνη αφής όπως το iPad</description>
    <description lang="en">Skin designed from the ground up to be used on touch screen devices or Android TV's used with a Fly Mouse or Wireless Mouse.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Skin designed from the ground up to be used on touch screen devices like the iPad</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</description>
    <description lang="es">Skin creada desde cero especialmente para dispositivos táctiles, como el iPad.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Skin creado desde cero especialmente para dispositivos táctiles, como el iPad.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Skin diseñado para uso en dispositivos con pantalla táctil como el iPad</description>
    <description lang="et">Spetsiaalselt puutetundlikele seadetele nagu iPad kasutamiseks disainitud rüü</description>
    <description lang="fi">Ulkoasu on suunniteltu alustalkaen käytettäväksi kosketusnäytöllisissä laitteissa, kuten iPad</description>
    <description lang="fr">Thème conçu en essence pour les écrans tactiles tel que l'Ipad</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Un habillage conçu à partir de zéro pour être utilisé sur les appareils à écran tactile comme l'iPad</description>
    <description lang="gl">Pel deseñada de cero para ser empregada en dispositivos táctiles</description>
    <description lang="he">המעטפת עוצבה מהיסוד עבור מכשירים בעלי מסך מגע כמו iPad</description>
    <description lang="hr">Presvlaka dizajnirana od temelja za korištenje na uređajima sa zaslonima osjetljivima na dodir kao što je iPad</description>
    <description lang="hu">A felszín elkészítésének célja az, hogy használható legyen az olyan érintőképernyős eszközökön is mint az iPad.</description>
    <description lang="is">Viðmót sem er hannað frá grunni til notkunar á tækjum með snertiskjá svo sem iPad</description>
    <description lang="it">Skin ideata per essere usata su periferiche touch screen come l'iPad</description>
    <description lang="ja">iPad などのタッチスクリーン端末専用に開発されたスキン</description>
    <description lang="ko">iPad 같은 터치 스크린 장치에서 사용하도록 완전히 새롭게 디자인한 스킨</description>
    <description lang="lt">Tema sukūrta naudojimui kompiuteriams, plančetėms su sensoriniu ekranu tokioms kaip iPad, Samsung, Asus ir t.t.</description>
    <description lang="lv">Apvalks dizainēts no pašiem pamatiem izmantošanai skārienekrāna ierīcēs, piemēram, iPad</description>
    <description lang="mk">Маска наново дизајнирана за користење со екрани на допир како што е iPad</description>
    <description lang="ms">Kulit direka dari sifar untuk digunakan pada peranti skrin sentuh seperti iPad</description>
    <description lang="nl">Skin is geheel opnieuw ontworpen om gebruikt te kunnen worden op apparaten met een aanraakscherm zoals de iPad</description>
    <description lang="no">Dette skallet er designet fra bunn for bruk på trykkfølsomme enheter som iPad</description>
    <description lang="pl">Skóra została zaprojektowana pod kątem urządzeń z ekranem dotykowym takich jak iPad </description>
    <description lang="pt">Tema desenvolvido de raiz para ser usado em ecrãs tácteis de dispositivos como o iPad</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Skin concebida do zero para ser usado em dispositivos com telas sensíveis ao toque, como o iPad</description>
    <description lang="ro">Skin realizat cu scopul de a fi utilizat pe dispozitive cu ecran de tip touch precum iPad</description>
    <description lang="ru">Обложка разработана с нуля для использования на устройствах с сенсорным экраном, например iPad</description>
    <description lang="se">Skal utformat från grunden för att användas på pekskärmsenheter som till exempel iPad</description>
    <description lang="sk">Vzhľad navrhnutý od základu pre použitie na zariadeniach s dotykovým displejom, ako napríklad iPad</description>
    <description lang="sl">Preobleka je zasnovana popolnoma na novo za naprave z zaslonom na dotik, kot je iPad</description>
    <description lang="sq">Maskë dizenjuar posaçërisht për tu përdorur me pajisjet me ekran me prekje si iPad’i</description>
    <description lang="sv">Skal designat från grunden för att användas på pekskärmsenhter som t.ex. iPad</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">தொடுதிரை சாதனங்களான iPad ஆகியவற்றிகான அலங்காரம்</description>
    <description lang="th">หน้าตาได้ถูกออกแบบขึ้นมาใหม่หมด เพื่อนำไปใช้กับอุปกรณ์หน้าจอสัมผ้ส เหมือน iPad</description>
    <description lang="tr">iPad gibi dokunmatik ekranlı cihazlarda kullanılmak üzere sıfırdan tasarlanmış dış görünüm</description>
    <description lang="uk">Обкладинка розроблена з нуля і призначена для використання на пристроях із сенсорним екраном, наприклад iPad.</description>
    <description lang="vi">Bộ skin được thiết kế lại từ đầu để sử dụng trên các thiết bị cảm ứng như iPad, Surface</description>
    <description lang="zh">完全为用于类似iPad的触屏设备而设计的皮肤</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">為了如 iPad 等擁有觸控螢幕的裝所重新設計的佈景主題</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af">Moenie hierdie omslag gebruik as daar nie 'n raak skerm of muis gekoppel is nie, of jy mag navigasie verloor</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar">لا تستخدم هذا الجلد إذا لم يكن لديك شاشة لمس أو الفأرة موصولة أو قد تفقد التوجيه</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="be">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">НЕ ползвайте облика ако устройството не е снабдено със сензорен екран или мишка, в противен случай ще загубите възможността за навигиране</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">No utilitzeu aquesta pell excepte si teniu una pantalla tàctil o un ratolí connectat, sinó podeu perdre la navegació</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Nepoužívejte tento vzhled pokud nemáte dotykovou obrazovku, nebo připojenou myš. Můžete ztratit kontrolu nad ovládáním aplikace</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cy">Peidiwch defnyddio'r croen hwn oni bai fod gennych sgrin cyffwrdd neu lygoden wedi ei gysylltu neu byddwch yn colli'r gallu i reoli.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Brug ikke dette skin medmindre du enten har en touchscreen eller mus forbundet, ellers kan du miste navigeringen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Verwenden Sie diese Skin nur wenn Sie einen Touch-Screen haben oder eine Maus angeschlossen ist, andernfalls kann die Steuerung ausfallen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Μην χρησιμοποιήσετε αυτό το κέλυφος αν δεν έχετε είτε μία οθόνη αφής ή ένα ποντίκι συνδεδεμένο διότι μπορεί να χάσετε τη δυνατότητα πλοήγησης</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">Do not use this skin unless you have either touch screen or a mouse connected or you may lose navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">No uses esta skin a no ser que tengas un dispositivo táctil o un ratón conectado, puesto que puedes perder la posibilidad de moverte por las opciones.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">No uses este skin a no ser que tengas un dispositivo táctil o un mouse conectado, ya que puedes perder la posibilidad de moverte por las opciones.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">No uses éste skin a menos de que tengas una pantalla táctil o un mouse conectado o puedes perder la navegación</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="et">Ära kasuta seda rüüd, kui sul puudub kas puutetundlik ekraan või ühendatud hiir. Vastasel juhul võid kaotada navigeerimise võimaluse</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fi">Älä käytä tätä skiniä ellei sinulla ole kosketusnäyttöä tai hiirtä liitettynä, koska saatat</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">N'utiliser ce thème qu'avec écran tactile ou souris sous peine d'en perdre le contrôle</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Ne pas utiliser cet habillage sauf si vous avez un écran tactile ou une souris connectée, sinon vous risquez de perdre la navigation</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">Non empregar esta pel a non ser que teña ben un dispositivo táctil ou un rato conectado. Pode perder a navegación.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">אין להשתמש במעטפת זו ללא מסך מגע או עכבר מחובר, אחרת לא ניתן יהיה לנווט במעטפת</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr">Ne koristite ovu presvlaku ukoliko nemate zaslon osjetljiv na dodir ili spojeni miš, u suprotnom možete izgubiti upravljivost računalom</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Ha a felszínt érintőképnyő nélkül, vagy egérrel használod, nem fog működni a navigálás</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="is">Notaðu ekki þetta viðmót nema þú hafir annaðhvort snertiskjá eða mús tengda, annars gætir þú tapað stjórninni á tækinu</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Non usare questa skin se non hai un touch screen o un mouse connesso, o potresi perdere la navigazione</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ja">タッチスクリーンやマウスが接続されていない端末でこのスキンを使うと、操作出来なくなる可能性があります。</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">터치 스크린이나 마우스가 없는 상황에서 이 스킨을 사용하지 마십시오. 탐색이 불가능할 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Šios temos vartoti negalima, nebent Jūs turite jutiklinį ekraną, arba prijungtą pelę kitaip Jūs galite prarasti naršymą/navigaciją</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lv">Nelietojiet šo apvalku, ja vien nav pieslēgts skārienekrāns vai pele, citādi varat zaudēt iespēju navigēt</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">Не користи маска доколку немас екран на допир или маус, може да ја загубиш навигацијата</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms">Jangan guna kulit ini melainkan anda mempunyai skrin sentuh atau tetikus yang bersambung atau anda kehilangan navigasi</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Gebruik deze skin niet tenzij u gebruik maakt van een aanraakscherm of muis anders kan je de besturing verliezen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="no">Ikke bruk dette skallet med mindre du har en touch skjerm, eller en mus tilkoblet da du kan miste muligheten til å navigere i Kodi</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Nie używaj tej skóry jeśli nie posiadasz ekranu dotykowego lub podłączonej myszki, w przeciwnym razie możesz stracić możliwość nawigacji</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Não utilize este tema se não tiver um ecrã táctil ou um rato, pois irá perder opções de navegação.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Não use essa skin a menos que você tenha uma tela sensível ao toque ou um mouse conectado, ou você pode perder a navegação</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ro">Nu folosiți acest skin dacă nu aveți un ecran de tip touch sau dacă nu aveți un mouse conectat sau veți pierde navigabilitatea</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Не включайте эту обложку при отсутствии сенсорного экрана или мыши, потому что возможна потеря управления.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="se">Använd inte detta skal om du inte har endera en pekskärmsenhet eller om mus, annars kan navigeringen sluta fungera</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Nepoužívajte tento vzhľad, pokiaľ nemáte dotykovú obrazovku, alebo pripojenú myš, inak môžete stratiť kontrolu nad ovládaním aplikácie</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">Ne uporabljajte te preobleke, če nimate zaslona na dotik ali povezane miške, ker boste s tem izgubili možnost navigacije</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sq">Mos e përdorni këtë maskë nëse nuk keni, ose ekran me prekje, ose maus te lidhur, përndryshe mund të humbni aftësinë për të naviguar</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Använd inte detta skal om du inte har endera en pekskärmsenhet eller en mus ansluten, annars kan du tappa bort navigeringen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ta_IN">தொடுதிரை அல்லது சுட்டி சாதனம் இல்லாமல் இந்த அலங்காரத்தை உபயோகிக்கவேண்டாம்</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="th">อย่าได้ใช้หน้าตานี้ จนกว่าคุณจะมี หน้าจอสัมผัส หรือ เมาส์ อย่างใดอย่างหนึ่งเชื่อมต่ออยู่ ไม่เช่นนั้นคุณจะสูญเสียการควบคุม</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tr">Bir dokunmatik ekranınız ya da fareniz olmadan bu dış görünümü kullanmayın, kontrolü kaybedebilirsiniz.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="uk">Використовуйте цю обкладинку, лише якщо ваш пристрій обладнано сенсорним екраном або мишею. Інакше ви можете втратити можливість керування.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="vi">Không sử dụng skin này trừ khi là bạn đang sử dụng màn hình cảm ứng hoặc sử dụng chuột để tránh trường hợp mất điều khiển</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">在非触屏且没有鼠标控制的情况下使用此皮肤会造成无法控制设备</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">除非你有觸控螢幕或滑鼠連接，否則請不要使用這個佈景主題，不然你會無法控制 Kodi。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
