<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.javstream" name="JAVStream" version="0.92.3" provider-name="ptom">
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.2" /> 
        <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" version="3.0.12" />
    </requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">JavStream</summary>
		<description lang="en">[COLOR yellow]Jav Stream[/COLOR] - Bringing JAV to Kodi! For all your Japanese AV Idol and Gravure Idol needs! Pulling streams from the most popular JAV websites.</description>
        <news>JAVStream v0.92.3(31st October 2016)
- Fixed issue so status dialog reflects the correct amount of sites processed
- Fixed issue stopping JAVHDFree, Jav-Stream, StreamJavPorn, JPIdols, StreamingJAV displaying results
- Fixed bug which caused infinite loop if canceling a search
- Fixed bug that stopped search results showing if term had already been searched for
- Fixed bug that stopped sources list showing for some videos
- Fixed issue from JAV4K from displaying results in search
- Fixed Flashx playback (still needs 100%)
- Fixed Kodi17 bug that would cause Source Search dialog to appear again over the playing video
- Fixed error which caused translation to crash when over quota
- Rewrote uncensored code for all providers to display more results
- Rewrote video sources to be ordered by qualtiy first 
- Added Xonline, FreeJav, Javocado, Popjav, Jav18, JAVUS, JAVGo, GAIMUP
- Added support for BigFile, vidto.me, RapidVideo, qwertycdn playback
- Up'd default timeout from 10 seconds to 20 seconds
- Removed EroPoi, JAV69, JavShow, IkuJAV, JAVStream365, JAVWest, JavZab, Korean720, PhimSexJav, Terlarng, YouJAV
- Temprarily taken off JavPortal, fix in next update</news>
        <forum>https://forums.tvaddons.ag/addon-releases/50629-jav-stream-japanese-xxx-adult-plugin-av-gravure-idol-streams.html</forum>
        <website>http://www.ptom.co.uk</website>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<language>en</language>
		<email>ptom98@gmail.com</email>
	</extension>
</addon>
